VENUS YUNG LAI YAN

+852 9387 2131 📞 venusyung1@gmail.com ✓ www.linkedin.com/in/laiyan-yung in



OBJECTIVE

Experienced Senior Consultant with a demonstrated history of working in the management consulting industry. Professional in IT Auditing, Cyber Security Assessment. Strong consulting professional with a Bachelor of Computer Science focused in Computer System from Western Washington University.



EXPERIENCE

Senior Consultant, Technology Risk, Business Consulting | Ernst & Young SEP 2020 - NOW

Provide IT assurance and consulting services to the client companies. Experienced in handling clients from various industries, including Banks and Securities. Participated in several independent compliance assessments for Hong Kong and overseas banks regarding Supervisory Policy Manuals and related circulars issued by the Hong Kong Monetary Authority.

Consultant, Technology Risk, Business Consulting | Ernst & Young SEP 2018 - SEP 2020

Conducted multiple large-scale IT general controls assessments, application controls assessments, and data analysis by applying computer-assisted audit techniques (CAATs) for a wide range of clients, including banks, securities firms, insurance firms, retail and entertainment firms.



SKILLS

- (
- SQL
- Python

- UNIX/LINUX
- English
- Chinese (Mandarin & Cantonese)



CERTIFICATIONS/ MEMBERSHIP

Certified Data Privacy Solution Engineer (CDPSE) – 2020

Information Systems Audit and Control Association (ISACA)

Certified Information System Auditor (CISA) – 2020

Information Systems Audit and Control Association (ISACA)



EDUCATION

Western Washington University | BSc, Computer Science 2015 - 2018

Specializing in the computer system, data structure, and database systems